Software Engineer

IAMIE LEVINER

U 0123 456789

iohndoe.com

n johnyD

EXPERIENCE

ACS Technologies

Software Engineer | July 2017 - present

Programming and watching cute cat videos.

ACS Technologies

Frontend Developer | January 2015 - December 2015

Fulfillment of extremely important tasks.

ACS Technologies

Trainee | March 2014 - December 2014

Making coffee and baking cookies.

EDUCATION

Major in Hacking and Computer Penetration, University A, New York, USA.

Master of Arts | March 2012 - December 2013

Major in Engineering, University B, Los Angeles, USA.

Bachelor of Science | March 2009 - December 2011

SKILLS

Also proficient in Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator, grew up bilingual (English and Klingon).

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript

- Node.js
- Angular 2
- TypeScript
- ES.Next
- Docker

About me

For the past 5 years, I have worked as a full stack software engineer with a concentration on front-end architecture, frameworks, and tooling. I am strongly interested in becoming part of a development culture that improves and enables its people, and I am looking forward to facing some new challenges.